<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on keyboardcrunch</title>
    
    
    
    <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on keyboardcrunch</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© keyboardcrunch</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 21:12:25 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun With Wireguard</title>
      <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/fun-with-wireguard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 21:12:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/fun-with-wireguard/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          After a recent conversation I realized that some folks have a narrow view of what can be done with Wireguard, and VPN connections in general. Though recently a number of toolsets/frameworks tailored for networking of containers or &amp;ldquo;bolt on zero-trust&amp;rdquo; networking have expanded that perception. My goal with this post is to highlight some software leveraging Wireguard, and to list a few different use-cases and reasons for using Wireguard (over traditional VPN or ZeroTier).
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Email Security</title>
      <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/email-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 14:42:21 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/email-security/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          This post started as a quick note for securing email for unused domains but I decided I could expand upon it a bit more to define terms in a language I believe to be more clear than I&amp;rsquo;ve seen elsewhere, and from the view-point of an administrator or domain owner.
Index  SPF DMARC DKIM Securing Unused Domains Additional Resources  SPF Sender Policy Framework (SPF) is a method for defining domains or ips that are allowed to send email for your domain.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going Static</title>
      <link>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/going-static/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 17:46:04 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://keyboardcrunch.github.io/posts/going-static/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          For the last few years I&amp;rsquo;ve been using either Wordpress or (usually) Ghost for my blogs, and self-hosting them. I&amp;rsquo;ve posted a mix of content including home-brewing, fermentation projects, posts describing code projects on my Github, and even rants and reviews. Due to a few failures on my part with backups and migrations, mainly with the images and static content, my blog has ended up missing some content and isn&amp;rsquo;t as clean as I&amp;rsquo;d like it to be.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>